campmor.com 2009-03-18

# Campmor: Online Privacy Policy

### Your Privacy Rights

Campmor is committed to the protection of your privacy. The following statement will explain, in greater depth, Campmor's Privacy Policy. If you have questions, you may send e-mail to our customer service department, at any time, using this page or email them at [customer-service@campmor.com](mailto:customer-service@campmor.com) or you can reach them by telephone, toll free, at 1-800-525-4784 during the following hours:

**Monday - Friday**
    8:30am - 9:30pm, Eastern Time 
**Saturday**
    8:30am - 6:00pm, Eastern Time 

**Customer Service is closed Sundays, Memorial Day, Independence Day, Labor Day, Thanksgiving, Christmas, and New Years Day.**

Overseas? Call us at (201) 335-9064.

For general information about Campmor, and our presence online please send email to [info@campmor.com](mailto:info@campmor.com)

Except as provided in the Privacy Policy, when placing an online order with Campmor, the information that we collect from you, is used solely for the purpose of processing your order and servicing your account. We need your name, e-mail address, credit card billing address, contact phone number, credit card number and expiration date. This information allows us to process your order and provides us with a way to contact you, should we have a question concerning your current order. After you place an online order with Campmor, a copy of that order is sent to you via email for your records. 

When you place an order, with Campmor, you are given the option of joining Trailmail®, an electronic mailing list for announcing special sales and other general announcements of interest to our customers. 

To subscribe to the Trailmail® mailing list, please send an email message to: 

In the body of the message write "subscribe trailmail firstname lastname" (without the quotes) please leave the subject line blank. 

To unsubscribe send an email message to: 
    In the body of the message write "unsubscribe trailmail" (without the quotes) please leave the subject line blank. 

**Campmor does not send unsolicited email, or spam.**

**Campmor will never sell, rent or distribute your e-mail address to any other company or organization.**

Once you have ordered from us, or have filled out our printed catalog request form, you will begin to receive our mail order catalog. We mail this catalog seven times a year. We occasionally make our customer list of names and addresses available to carefully screened retailers and outdoor related organizations whose products and activities might be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive such mailings from us or third parties, please copy your mailing label exactly and mail it to:

> Campmor Mail Preference Service  
> PO Box 680  
> Mahwah, NJ 07430

Or you can send e-mail to our customer service department, at any time, using this page or email them at [customer-service@campmor.com](mailto:customer-service@campmor.com) or you can reach them by telephone, toll free, at 1-800-525-4784 during the following hours:

**Monday - Friday**
    8:30am - 9:30pm, Eastern Time 
**Saturday**
    8:30am - 6:00pm, Eastern Time 

Some areas of our site link to other web sites. Although we make every effort to select sites that we feel will be of interest to our customers, we cannot guarantee your privacy when visiting these sites.

* * *

### Campmor's Use of Cookies

To shop online with Campmor, your internet browser must be set to allow cookies, a small bit of text used by your browser to uniquely identify you to our web server. If your browser is set to reject cookies you will not be able to add anything to your shopping cart. We use cookies to make sure that when you add something to your shopping cart it goes into your cart and not someone elses. We also use cookies to track how many unique visitors we have daily and general buying trends within our site. This information is only for Campmor's internal use and will never be distributed to any other parties. The cookie is set to expire as soon as you quit your browser, so if you return to our website you will have to accept the cookie again.

* * *

### Security

Campmor uses the latest encryption technology and other methods to protect your credit card information. Campmor recommends using the latest version of either Netscape Communicator/Navigator or Microsoft's Internet Explorer web browsers. If you are using one of these browsers (and are not using a proxy server) all transactions are fully encrypted and secure via Secure Sockets Layer.

* * *

### Updates and Revisions

If you are a registered shopper, Campmor saves and maintains billing and shipping contact information, as well as an address book with shipping addresses of family and friends. If you wish to review or change any of this information, simply login and click the 'Edit account information' link. 

Any material changes to this privacy policy will be posted prominently on our web page. We do recommend that you occasionally re-visit this page and review our privacy policy periodically.

In order to be opt out from your information being collected for analysis, click on [ Opt-Out](http://www.campmor.com/html/opt_out.shtml)

Campmor's Privacy Policy is effective as of August 11, 1999.
